[
    {
		"question": "Эффективность (Производительность)",
		"answer": "Performance"
	},
    {
		"question": "Сложение",
		"answer": "Addition"
	},
    {
		"question": "Вычитание",
		"answer": "Substraction"
	},
    {
		"question": "Умножение",
		"answer": "Multiplication"
	},
    {
		"question": "Деление",
		"answer": "Division"
	},
    {
		"question": "Сравнение",
		"answer": "Comparing"
	},
    {
		"question": "Выбор",
		"answer": "Selection"
	},
    {
		"question": "Дело",
		"answer": "Deal"
	},
    {
		"question": "Получать",
		"answer": "Obtain"
	},
    {
		"question": "Выполнять",
		"answer": "Execute"
	},
    {
		"question": "Цифровой",
		"answer": "Digital"
	},
    {
		"question": "Вместимость",
		"answer": "Capacity"
	},
    {
		"question": "Еденицы",
		"answer": "Units"
	},
    {
		"question": "Единицы измерения",
		"answer": "Unit"
	},
    {
		"question": "Постоянный",
		"answer": "Permanent"
	},
    {
		"question": "Широкий",
		"answer": "Wide"
	},
    {
		"question": "Цель",
		"answer": "Target"
	},
    {
		"question": "Короткий (краткий)",
		"answer": "Brief"
	}
]
